

WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Music teacher and Front-end enthusiast who enjoys learning new technologies, creating beautiful websites and overall making the user have a great experience. When it comes to designing, I am a perfectionist. I am a person that's easy to get along with, and am always striving to improve myself, both as a developer and as a person.

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer at Mercado Libre (oct 2021 - present) - Front-end development using React, Sass and TypeScript, for the biggest e-commerce platform in Latin America.

Front-end Developer at SEIS S.A. (mar 2021 - oct 2021) - Development of web apps related to the field of electricity, using Next.js in conjunction with TypeScript and Styled Components.

Teaching Assistant at Henry (dec 2020 - feb 2021, may 2021 - aug 2021) - My role was to guide students, help them understand core concepts and reinforce the theory by providing explanations and extracurricular projects.

EDUCATION

Henry Bootcamp (oct. 2020 - feb. 2021) - Fullstack Developer. 700+ hours of intensive learning. The technologies learned there include HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Node, Express, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Github, and the SCRUM methodology.

"Luis Gianneo" College of Music, Mar del Plata (dec. 2010 - dec. 2020) - Music Teacher

SKILLS AND SOFTWARE

HTML	Less & Sass	React	Node.js	PostgreSQL	Adobe XD & Figma
CSS	Tailwind CSS	Redux	Express	Next.js	Adobe Photoshop

JavaScript GraphQL TypeScript Sequelize Jest & Cypress Git & Github

CONTACT

https://emiliano-alfonso.vercel.app

emilianoalfonso1989@gmail.com